{
  "hardquestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is 25 - 17?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "9",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 34 - 19?",
      "answer1": "15",
      "answer2": "16",
      "correct": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 27 - 14?",
      "answer1": "12",
      "answer2": "13",
      "correct": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 42 - 29?",
      "answer1": "12",
      "answer2": "13",
      "correct": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 56 - 37?",
      "answer1": "18",
      "answer2": "19",
      "correct": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 48 - 26?",
      "answer1": "21",
      "answer2": "22",
      "correct": "22"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 39 - 18?",
      "answer1": "21",
      "answer2": "22",
      "correct": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 63 - 34?",
      "answer1": "29",
      "answer2": "30",
      "correct": "29"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 55 - 28?",
      "answer1": "26",
      "answer2": "27",
      "correct": "27"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 72 - 46?",
      "answer1": "25",
      "answer2": "26",
      "correct": "26"
    }
  ]
}
